婚礼承包商给我12道开胃菜的清单  我得减到6道
So the wedding caterer sent me this list of 12 appetizers. I have to narrow down it to six.
食物问题  交给我吧
Food? Oh, give me.
摩妮卡跟你们提过我们结婚时  要请《摇摆国王》来演唱吗
So did Monica tell you about this great band called the Swing Kings that we're trying to get to play at the wedding?
你什么时候喜欢上摇摆音乐
Since when are you into swing music?
好久以前就喜欢了  我曾跑遍全城听乐团演奏
Oh since forever. I used to go all over town listening to bands.
钱德  在GAP的广告里看到的
Chandler. Gap commercial.
那你预订了吗  打电话了吗  我会打的
So did you book them? Did you call? I will.
你要我打吗  我会打的  你只需要做好你的工作
You want me to call? No. I'll do it. You just stick to your job.
你的工作是什么  别碍事
What is your job? Staying out of the way.
不可能再减了  摩尼卡  你为什么不15样全选了呢
This is impossible Monica, Why don't you just pick all 15?
只有12道而已  没错  我加了三道
There were only 12. Oh, yeah, I added three.
什么是花生酱手指
What are "peanut-butter fingers"?
老友记  第七季  第17集  廉价婚纱
Friends  S07E17  The One With The Cheap Wedding Dress
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
哦  你好
Well, hello.
她好可爱
She's cute.
我们是不是该上去和她聊聊啊
Should we go try to talk to her?
当然  订婚的一大好处就是跟美女说话  不会感到紧张了
Sure. That's one of the great thing about being engaged, I'm not nervous to talk to pretty girls anymore.
你们能过来帮帮我吗
Could you guys help me?
我来帮你搬那个
Yeah, let me get that for you.
它真的很重  没问题
It's really heavy. I got it.
嗨  我是罗斯  他是我朋友钱德
So hi, I'm Ross, and this is my friend, Chandler.
我是克丽丝汀
I'm Kristen.
克丽丝汀  嗨  你刚搬来吗
Kristen. Hi. Are you new to the area?
如果你刚搬来这里  我可以带你四处参观一下
Because if you are, I'd love to show you around sometime.
事实上  我从四条街外搬来这里
I actually just moved from four blocks over. Oh.
但这里好像另外一个世界
But this block is like a whole other world.
事实上这个地区的历史非常有趣
Y'know actually , it does have a very interesting history.
这条街是纽约第一条有下水道系统的街道
This street is the first street in the city to have an underground sewer system.
之前污水跟废弃物
Before that, sewage and waste...
会直接流到街上
...would just flow right down the street. Yeah.
有时深及脚踝
Sometimes ankle-deep.
说的好
Smooth.
你说什么
Excuse me?
搬完家后你一定会饿  不如晚上我带你去吃饭怎么样
You're gonna be starving after moving. What do you say I take you to dinner tonight?
我很乐意  真的太棒了
I'd like that. Yeah? Great.
我帮你把箱子搬上去
Let me take this up for you.
你先请  不  你先请
After you. Oh, no. After you.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
是我疯了  还是真的很配我啊
Am I crazy, or does this totally go?
我的天啊  你看起来好漂亮
Oh, my God! You look so beautiful!
谢谢你  瑞秋  但看看摩妮卡
Thank you, Rachel. But look at Monica!
就是它  没错  就是这件
This is it. Yeah, this is the one.
我不敢相信我终于找到了
I can't believe I found it.
你看起来好漂亮  如果我认识你  我会哭的
Wow, you look so beautiful. If I knew you, I'd cry.
我是摩妮卡盖勒  尽量哭吧
I'm Monica Geller. Ball like a baby.
我是梅根巴利
I'm Megan Bailey.
你找到婚纱了吗  没有  这些婚纱都很漂亮
Have you found your dress yet? Oh no, These dresses are all so amazing...
但我买不起  我也是
...but there is no way I couldn't afford one. No, I can't afford this either.
我只来这里找婚纱  然后我会到克莱门婚纱店买  同样的东西那里有打折
No. I-I-I’m, I'm just to figure out the one I want, then I'll get it at Kleinman's, this discount place in Brooklyn,
后天  那里有个大甩卖
Day after tomorrow, they're having a huge sale.
谢谢你的情报  你什么时候结婚
Thanks for the tip. Yeah! So-so when are you getting married?
哦  我不是  我只是喜欢试穿婚纱  跟我一样
Oh I'm not. I just like to try these on. I do the same thing.
我只是在开玩笑  我7月25号结婚
I'm just kidding. I'm getting married July 25th.
我也只是在开玩笑
I'm just kidding too. Ha, ha.
我12月结婚
I'm getting married in December.
你什么时候结婚  五月十五日
So when are you getting married? Oh May 15th.
哦  很快  是的  你请谁拍照
Ooh. It's getting close. Yeah! So who's your photographer?
杰佛瑞   我们见过他
Jeffrey. We met with him.
他拿裸体婚纱照给你们看了吗  那个伴郎吗  哇
Did he show you the photos of the nude wedding photos? The best man? Wow!
我知道  我差点取消了婚礼
I know. I almost called off my wedding. Heh, heh, heh.
你请了哪个乐团  我未婚夫想请《摇摆国王》
Oh, who's your band? My  fiancee wants The Swing Kings.
你真幸运  我未婚夫想请《尸体》  那重金属乐团
Oh, you're so lucky. My fiancee wants the heavy metal band, Carcass.
是"湿"体还是"尸"体  那不重要  他们都很棒
Is that spelled with a "C" or a "K"? Oh, my God, it doesn't matter, they're both great!
你知道吗  你知道吗  别在这里买婚纱
Oh, you know what? you know what? Don't buy that here.
现在你知道你喜欢哪一件  到克莱门婚纱店买  才半价
Now that you know what you want you should go to Kleinman's and get it half off.
这里的婚纱太贵了
This place is so over-priced.
我是这里的老板
I own this store.
这件婚纱有别的颜色吗  还是
So does this come in another color, or...
嗨  你要搬进来还是搬走
Hi. You moving in or moving out?
我要搬进来  需要我帮忙吗
Moving in. Can I give you a hand?
好吧  但是你得小心一点  来帮我的那个人因为背痛先走了
Okay, but be careful. The guy who was helping before had to leave because he hurt his back.
他是你男朋友  不是
Boyfriend? No.
我是乔伊
I'm Joey.
我是克丽丝汀
Kristen.
你的名字真好听
Wow. What a beautiful name.
你说你叫什么来着
What is it again?
克丽丝汀  对了
Kristen. Ah, that's it. Okay.
你住在附近  是啊  我就住在那边
So uh, do you live around here? Yeah. Yeah, right down there.
我得提供你一些资讯
Let me give you a tip.
别在那个楼梯上睡觉   醒来时你的鞋子可能已经被偷了
Don't take a nap on this stoop. You could wake up without shoes gone.
我会记住的  嗯
I'll remember that. Okay.
听着  今晚你要跟我一起吃饭吗
Listen, would you uh, would you like to have dinner with me tonight?
今晚我有约了  明天可以吗
I have plans tonight. Oh. But how about tomorrow?
听起来不错  这个要搬到哪里
Sounds great. Well, where does this go?
你看起来很壮  把它交给我  你去帮我搬箱子吧
You look strong. I'll take that, you grab one of the boxes.
好啊
Okay. Yeah.
（书  枕头）
对  我还是搬这个吧
Yeah, I'll get this one.
（克莱门婚纱店五折大减价）
真是的
Come on.
这里就是布鲁克林
So this is Brooklyn?
好  听着  通常每件婚纱  一个尺寸只有一件
All right, listen up. There's usually only one dress in each size.
他们一开门   我们马上冲进去
So when they open those doors, fan out.
这就是你们的目标  记住它
Now, this is what you're looking for. Memorize it.
找到婚纱后就吹哨子  好吗
When you locate the dress blow on these, all right?
用力吹三声  一听到哨音后  马上跑过来
Three sharp blasts. When you hear it, come running.
好  知道了
Okay, got it. All right.
他来了
Here he comes!
她们在推我   别那么孩子气
Oh, they're pushing! Don't be a baby!
别档路  我们冲吧
Out of the way! Let's go!
瑞秋  快一点
Hey, Rachel! Come on!
不  不  不是  不是
No. No, not it. Not it. Not it. Ugh.
别推我
Don't crowd me.
就是它   就是这件  我的天啊  婚纱太完美了
This is it! This is the dress! Oh, my God. It's perfect.
对不起  这件是我的
I'm sorry, this one's taken! Whoa!
梅根  摩妮卡
Megan! Monica!
你来了  对
You came! Yeah!
这是我的婚纱  不
This is my dress! No!
没错  它就是  你看见我穿过得  现在你会看到我买下它
Yes, it is. You saw me wearing it. And now you'll see me buying it.
什么  你这个疯子
What? You freak!
如果没有我你根本不知道这个地方
You wouldn't even know about this place if it wasn't for me!
听着  你不会想跟我争  也许我想呢  我很凶的
Look, you don't want to fight me. Maybe I do. I'm pretty feisty!
我来了  我来了  嘿
I'm coming! I'm coming! Hey!
好了  嘿
Okay! Hey.
我该上哪边
Oh, what do I do?!
你在干什么  找到婚纱了吗
What are you doing? Did you find the dress?
你找到婚纱了吗
Did you find the dress?
不  快把我弄出去  菲比  这些女人看见打折都疯了
No. You gotta get me out of here Phoebe! These bargain shoppers are crazy.
我们得去找摩妮卡  不  你得抓住我的手
We've gotta get Monica. No! You gotta hold my hand!
天啊
Oh, my God.
对不起  借过
Excuse me! Excuse me!
快走  快走
Go! Go! Go!
快走  马上
Hey "Go! Now !!
（中央咖啡厅）
罗斯  前几天的约会怎么样
So, Ross, how was your date the other night?
你和她谈起过那次冲洗厕所的奇妙之旅了
Did you tell her about the magical ride that starts with the flush of every toilet?
尽管笑吧  但她给我留言  说她想再跟我约会
Laugh all you want, but she left me a message saying she'd like to go out again.
事实上  我正要打电话给她
Oh. In fact, I'll go call her right now.
我一定会告诉她   我的朋友钱德说
And I'll make sure and tell her my friend Chandler says...
嘿  钱德  嘿
Hey, Chandler. Hey.
抱歉昨晚我失约了  我刚好有个约会
Listen, sorry I didn't stop by last night, but I had a date.
乔伊  那快凌晨一点  就算没过来也没关系
Uh Joe, when it's 1:00 in the morning and you don't come by? That's okay.
我跟一个辣妹约会  她刚刚搬到对面街
Well check it out. It was with this really hot girl who just moved in right across the street.
真的吗  她就住在对面街  对
Really? Right across the street? Yeah.
你什么时候认识她的   两天前
When did you meet her? Two days ago.
太棒了
Excellent!
罗斯也认识了个女孩  是吗
You know, Ross met somebody too. Oh, yeah?
嘿  怎么样
Hey. How'd it go?
太棒了  我们星期六要再出去玩
Great. We're going out again Saturday.
但我刚刚发现她也在跟别人约会
But I just found out she's also seeing some other guy.
真的吗
Really?
乔伊  如果你是罗斯你会怎么做
Joe, what would you do if you were in Ross' situation?
我跟他差不多  跟我约会的女孩也在跟别人约会
Well, I sort of am. I'm dating this girl who's also seeing another guy.
但我一点都不担心
But I'm not too worried about it.
你不必担心  但相信我  我可不想当你的竞争者
Well you shouldn't be. Believe me, I wouldn't want to be the guy who's up against you.
那个混蛋一定会输的
I mean, that doofus is going to lose.
真的太有趣了
So this is nice.
真希望我能留下来  相信我
I wish I didn't have to go. Believe me.
但不幸的是我得走了
But I unfortunately have to.
对了  顺便问下  跟你们约会的女孩叫什么名字
Oh uh, By the way, what's the name of the girl you're dating?
克丽丝汀莱  再见
Kristen Leigh. Bye.
很明显  我们之中  只有一个人能继续跟她约会
Well, obviously, only one of us can keep dating her.
没错  我们该怎么决定
Obviously. So how do we decide?
好了  我们得客观地来解决这件事
Well now, let's look at this objectively.
我想我该跟她约会
I think I should date her.
或是我该跟她约会
Or I'm the one who dates her.
太有趣了  但是听好了  我跟她约会
That's interesting. But check this out. I date her.
好吧  但是换个角度来说
Yeah, I like that. But just to go in another direction--
好吧  这样我们是谈不出结论来的
Okay. okay. This can go on for a while.
没错  我们该点些吃的  不  乔伊
Yeah well we should order some food then. No, Joey.
听着  我们为什么不让她来决定呢
Look, why don't, why don't we just let her decide, okay?
我们都再跟她约会一次
We'll each go out with her one more time.
看看她更喜欢谁
And we'll see who she likes best.
听起来很公平
That sounds fair.
或许我会带她到新开的法国餐厅吃饭
Maybe I'll take her to that new French restaurant down the street.
等一下  我们得对约会费用设下限制
Ah yeah. Wait a second. Look we're gonna have to set a spending limit on the date.
我可没有钱带她去高级餐厅吃饭
I don't have the money to take her to a fancy place like that.
那只有抱歉了  但那是我的约会方式
Well, sorry. That's what I do on dates.
好吧  我想我也有我的方式
All right. Well, I guess I'll just have to do what I do on dates.
我们来决定费用限制  好吧
So let's decide on a spending limit. Yeah.
再加一片
And a slice...
六块钱
Six dollars?
我想是一百块  好吧
I was thinking more like a hundred. Okay.
你能借我94块吗
Can I borrow 94 dollars?
我知道  你能帮我拿张面纸吗
I know. Can you hand me a tissue?
你家没有健怡可乐了
You're out of Diet Coke.
喂
Hello?
什么  你什么
What? You what?
你给我听好了  小姐
You listen here, missy!
什么
What?
是那个梅根打来的  她订下《摇摆国王》  日期是我们结婚的那一天
That was that girl Megan. She booked The Swing Kings on the day of our wedding...
还说如果我不把婚纱让给她  我就没有乐团
...and said that I couldn't have them back unless I gave her the dress!
这么说的话  《尸体》乐队有空了
Does that mean Carcass is available?
我该怎么办  那件婚纱  就是我一直想要的
What am I gonna do? That's the dress! That is "the" dress!
钱德喜欢那个乐团  我该怎么办啊
Chandler wants the band. What do I do?
想办法说服他放弃  那怎么做呢
Well just figure out a way to talk him out of it. How?
你家卫生纸用完了
You're out of toilet paper!
嗨  怎么样
Hey. What's up?
我过来祝你约会顺利啊
I just wanted to come by and y'know,wish you good luck on your date.
谢谢  你们约几点
Oh thanks. What time are you meeting her?
我们在葛兰梅西餐厅  订了八点的位子
We have 8:00 reservations at Grand Merci Bistro.
时间只剩20分钟  你最好快去换衣服
Wow, that's in 2O minutes. You'd better get dressed.
我已经换好衣服了  太好了
I am dressed. Oh, well, good.
对我来说
For me.
这是什么  你在敷脸
What's this? Did you give yourself a facial?
我用油性护肤霜
I have an oily T-zone.
好吧  兄弟
Okay, dude.
你送克丽丝汀花  没错
Hey, you sent Kristen flowers? That's right.
你花了一百块  你把钱花光了  你完蛋了
You spent 100 dollars. That's the limit. You're screwed!
我在约会前送她花  所以技术上来说
Actually, I sent the flowers before the actual date, so technically...
技术上来说  我没有犯规  谢谢你来看我
...technically, I didn't break any rules. Thanks for stopping by though.
你要真的那么玩  我也可以犯规
Oh-oh! So that's the way it's gonna be? Yeah I can break the rules too. y'know!
那你打算怎么办  我不知道
Oh yeah? What are you gonna do? I don't know.
为什么我一点都不讶异  告诉你罗斯  我不会放过你的
Why am I not surprised? Y'know what Ross? I'm not gonna let you get away with this!
我想你没有太多的选择  我们走着瞧
I don't think you have much choice. Well we'll see!
再见  对  再见
Bye-bye. Yeah, bye-bye.
嘿  只要薄薄地敷一层就好
Hey! So just a light layer?
知道  只要敷这里跟这里
Yeah, just here and there.
乔伊又把肉酱滴在栏杆上了
Joey got meat sauce on the banister again.
摇摆音乐太落伍了
Yeah, swing music is so out.
菲比  他要在这房间里才听得到
Phoebe, he's gotta be in the room for that to work.
你们到底在说什么
What are you guys talking about?
我们在谈《摇摆国王》
Well umm, we were just talking about the y'know, the Swing Kings ...
讨论到底该不该请他们来
...and just wondering whether y'know, they were the right way to go.
有一次我去参加  请摇摆乐团来表演的婚礼
Yeah, I went to a wedding once where they had swing music...
两个月后他们就离婚了
...and two months later the couple got divorced.
我倒不是说这其中必有联系
And now I'm not saying there's any connection here y'know,...
但他们的确告诉我  那是他们离婚的原因
...but they did tell me that's why they got divorced.
但我喜欢摇摆音乐
But I love swing music!
但《摇摆国王》
Yeah but The Swing Kings?
他们烂到有人听他们的演唱会死掉  他们就那么死了
y'know they suck so much that people actually die at their concerts. They just stop living.
我只知道摩妮卡跟我  去看他们演唱时非常开心
Look all I know is when Monica and I went to see them, we had fun.
事实上还有一个原因
And there's another reason too.
是什么原因  我不想说
Well, what is the other reason? I don't want to say.
你非说不可  或许它很愚蠢
Well, you have to, because maybe it's stupid.
摩妮卡跟我  随着他们的音乐起舞时
Well it's just while Monica and I were dancing to them...
那是我第一次知道
...it was the first time I knew that...
你就是我想一辈子共舞的女人
...you were the woman that I wanted to dance all my dances with.
糟糕
Oh, crap.
我们的桌子  马上就准备好  太棒了
So they said our table will be ready in just a few minutes. Oh, great.
你的背好点了吗  没事了
Is your back feeling better? Oh yeah, it's fine.
我猜肌肉越多
I guess, ahem, the more muscles you have...
就越可能抽筋
...the more they can spasm out of control.
克丽丝汀  乔伊
Kristen? Joey!
嗨  嗨
Hi. Hi.
你来这里做什么  我喜欢这个地方
What are you doing here? Oh I like this place.
技术上来说  我没有犯规  所以
And technically, technically, I'm not breaking any rules, so...
罗斯  他是乔伊  乔伊  罗斯
Well, Ross, this is Joey. Joey, Ross.
嗨  嗨  很高兴能认识你
Hi. Hi. It's nice to meet you.
我以前有个朋友叫乔伊
I used to have a friend named Joey.
但他现在不是了
I don't anymore.
我们的桌子马上就准备好了
Our table will be ready in a couple minutes.
当然  我想跟你们一起等  谢谢
Sure! I would love to wait with you guys! Thanks!
乔伊  你看起来好眼熟
So Joey, you look familiar.
你上过电视或其它什么吗
Are you on TV or something?
乔伊不喜欢提这件事
Well Joey doesn't like to talk about it...
但他主演过《我们的日子》
...but he's one of the stars of Days of Our Lives.
没错  你不是演女人吗
That's right. That's right. Don't you play a woman?
那是被困在男人身体里的女人
A woman in a man's body.
这还好点
Much better.
你知道吗  罗斯  真有趣  因为我也觉得你很眼熟
So y'know Ross it's funny, because you look familiar to me too.
你结过婚吗
Have you ever been married?
是的  我结过婚
Yes, I have.
事实上  前几天
In fact, just the other day...
克丽丝跟我还谈到  我结过婚  有个儿子
...Kris and I talked about how I've been married and have a son.
小艾力克  没错  等下  不  是小班才对
Yeah, little Eric. That's right. Wait. No, Ben.
你只结过一次婚吗
So you've just been married the one time then?
嗯  你结过两次婚
Well, um... You've been married twice?
对  那个
Yes. And...
之后又结了一次
...another time after that.
天啊  我饿了
Boy, I'm getting hungry.
乔伊  你曾经在约会时饿到
Ahem. Hey, Joey, have you ever been so hungry on a date...
趁女伴去上洗手问  偷吃掉她的食物吗
...that when the girl goes to the bathroom, you eat some of her food?
你说服务生吃掉我的蟹饼
You said the waiter ate my crab cake.
罗斯  你的第一段婚姻  为什么会结束
Yeah. So, Ross, well now—why did that first marriage break up? Hm?
因为你前妻是异性恋  还是同性恋啊
Was it because the woman was straight or because she was a lesbian?
你们两个认识吗  不认识
Do you two know each other? No.
只是罗斯看起来像是  会跟有同性恋倾向的女人
No. It just seems like Ross is the kind of a guy that would marry a woman...
结婚后  逼得她非得出柜的男人
...on the verge of being a lesbian and then push her over the edge.
等一下  你不是淋病海报上的那个男的吗
Wait a minute! Were you on a poster for gonorrhea?
你跟猴子同床共枕过吧
Have you ever slept in the same bed with a monkey?
别把马塞尔扯进来
Hey, you leave Marcel out of this!
好吧  你曾经被自己的牛皮裤卡住了
Fine! You ever gotten stuck in a pair of your own leather pants?
嘿  嘿  你曾经把自己锁在电视柜里吗  性病小子
Hey, hey! Have you ever locked yourself in a TV cabinet, VD-boy?
猴子迷
Monkey-lover!
你觉得她是什么时候离开的
When do you think we lost her?
可能是淋病那一段吧
Probably around "gonorrhea."
甜心  我回来了  别进来
Hi, honey, I'm home! Don't come in here!
怎么了  你的另一个男朋友在里面吗
Why, do you have another boyfriend in there?
不  我们只会在他家鬼混
No. We only mess around at his place.
虽然是我开的头  但我开始担心了  你能出来吗
Y'know it's funny, I started it, but now it's scaring me, so could you come out here, please?
不行  我正在穿婚纱
No. I'm wearing a wedding dress.
你买到婚纱了  太棒了
You got a wedding dress? That's great.
对  但我要把它退回去  那我为什么不能看呢
Yeah, but I'm not keeping it. Well then why can't I see it?
我猜应该可以
Oh. I guess you can.
但我得把它退回去  所以你绝不能喜欢它
Okay but; I-I have to return it, so you can't like it.
好吧  我发誓  我保证会讨厌它
Okay, I promise. I'll hate it.
哇  你看起来好可怕
Wow. You look hideous.
真的吗
Really?
没错  那是我见过的最丑的婚纱
Yeah. That's like the most ugliest dress I've ever seen.
你为什么要把它退回去
Why do you have to return it?
因为它真的不合适
Oh because it doesn't really fit.
还有  我订了《摇摆国王》
Oh, by the way, I booked The Swing Kings.
那真的是太棒了  谢谢
Oh, that's great. Great. Thanks.
但那件婚纱可怕极了
But that dress, I mean, it's like, ugh, terrible.
真想把它从你身上扯下来  好吧
It makes me want to rip it right off you. Okay.
但你不可以把它弄破
Okay! But you can't rip it.
或许弄破点也没关系  好
Well, maybe a little. Okay.
你们想看看婚礼上  演唱歌曲的清单吗
Hey, guys, you want to look at the song list for the wedding?
怎么了
Guys?
我还以为你会去一整天
I thought you'd be gone all day.
好吧  发生了什么事
All right, what's going on?
对不起  或许我应该  让你们这些小女生独处一下
I’m sorry. I'm sorry. I should probably leave you girls alone.
尽管笑吧  但十分钟后  我们的皮肤会变得又白又嫩
Yeah, Laugh all you want, but in 1O minutes we'll have younger-looking skin.
对  没错
Yeah. Right there.
她也该敷一下脸的
You know, she could use a little...
好球  太帅了
Oh, nice shot! Yeah! Oh! Oh! Oh!